criminal-info.com 2015-06-07

# Criminal-Info.com - Privacy Policy

Criminal-Info.com or Criminal-info service is in no way affiliated or connected with the Government. By using this site, you confirm that you will use any information obtained for lawfully acceptable purposes. Please be advised that it is against the law to use the information obtained from this site to stalk or harass others. Search requests on public officials, juveniles, and/or celebrities are strictly prohibited. Users who request information under false pretenses or use data obtained from this site in contravention of the law may be subject to civil & criminal penalties. All searches are subject to terms of use and applicable law. Information contained herein is derived from records that may have errors and/or not always be accurate or complete. Any searches done on this page are for example only and will not display actual results until you are logged in as a member of the service. ** Please note that "results available", doesn't mean records are found. It can mean 0 records results are available. * Criminal Records are available nationwide, however some states are limited and may not provide the type of record you are seeking. *Offer Ends Today - But We Automatically Renew Everyday Until Further Notice.  When you use our service you are granted access to as many records as you want, freely. We do not charge per record or search. We only charge for the service and tech support we provide. Records and searches are free of charge for registered users, who may use them as many times as required. Disclaimer  

 **Criminal-info.com pledges to keep ANY information you provide private, and does not share it with anyone else, without your approval.**  

 **Our payment gateway is through Clickbank.com and their privacy is as follows:**  

 **ClickBank Privacy Policy**  

 **Click Sales Inc. (ClickBank) is committed to maintaining the privacy of personal information that you provide to us when using any of our online services. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the information we receive when you transmit data to any machine owned by ClickBank.**  

 **Web Form Information**  

 **When you submit information to ClickBank to make a payment or open an account, we may collect personally identifiable information from you that may include your name, address, email address, and credit card number. We do not knowingly collect personal information from persons under the age of eighteen.**  

 **Web Site Usage Information**  

 **We automatically collect IP addresses and Web site usage information from you when you access any of our online services. This information helps us evaluate how our visitors and subscribers use and navigate our Web sites on an aggregate basis, including but not limited to, the number and frequency of visitors and subscribers to each web page and the length of their visits.**  

 **How We Use Information Collected**  

 **We may use information in the following ways:**  

  *  **To perform the actions for which you specifically provided the information (For example, enabling us to process, validate, and verify purchases).  **  

  *  **To register you as a client and establish an account for you.  **  

  *  **To send you email notifications about our new or existing ClickBank products and services, special offers, or to otherwise contact you.  **  

  *  **To enhance existing features or develop new features, products and services.  **  

  *  **To provide advertisers and other third parties with aggregate information about our user base and usage patterns.  **  

  *  **To allow us to personalize the content and advertising that you and others see based on personal characteristics or preferences.  **  

 **Except as specifically set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your personally identifiable information with any entity outside of ClickBank.**  

 **We may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is necessary to enforce our service agreements or terms of use (for example to protect our intellectual property rights). We may also disclose or use your personal information when we, in good faith, believe that the law may require us to do so.**  

 **Cookies**  

 **We define a cookie as any string of data that is automatically stored on your computer upon access to our online services. ClickBank employs cookies to assign temporary identification numbers to machines that access our web servers. This information enables us to deliver faster service to our subscribers, prevent denial of service attacks on our systems, detect and prevent fraudulent transactions, and assist with awarding proper sales credit to our partners. All ClickBank cookies are 1) of limited duration, 2) less than 5KB in length, 3) only visible to ClickBank web servers, and 4) devoid of any personally identifiable information.**  

 **Security**  

 **The personally identifiable information we collect about you is stored in limited access servers. We maintain safeguards to protect the security of these servers and your personally identifiable information. We retain personally identifiable information only as long as necessary to complete a purchase, thwart fraud, provide customer service, or maintain your account with us.**  

 **Policy Modifications**  

 **We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically.**  

 **Comments and Questions**  

 **If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us by submitting your inquiry to ClickBank's  ** **[Customer Service department](https://www.clickbank.com/customer_service.html)** **.**
